Young Women's Christian Association (YWCA) Of Albany, New York Records
M. E. Grenander Department of Special Collections and Archives
- Photographs, 1911-1995; nam_apap137-5; 2.64 cubic ft.
  - Tribute to Women, Ceremony and Honorees, 1985; nam_apap137-5_52 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Tribute to Women, Ceremony and Honorees, 1986; nam_apap137-5_53 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Tribute to Women, Ceremony and Honorees, 1987; nam_apap137-5_54 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Tribute to Women, Ceremony and Honorees, 1988; nam_apap137-5_55 (Box 7, Folder 6-7)
  - Tribute to Women, Ceremony and Honorees, 1989; nam_apap137-5_56 (Box 7, Folder 8-9)
  - Tribute to Women, Ceremony and Honorees, 1990; nam_apap137-5_57 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Tribute to Women, Ceremony and Honorees, 1992; nam_apap137-5_58 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Tribute to Women, Ceremony and Honorees, 1993; nam_apap137-5_59 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Tribute to Women, Ceremony and Honorees, 1994; nam_apap137-5_60 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Tribute to Women, Ceremony and Honorees, Undated; nam_apap137-5_61 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Workshops, 1983-1984; 1987-1990; nam_apap137-5_62 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Workshops, Undated; nam_apap137-5_63 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - YWCA Buildings, Interior and Exterior, 1955; 1980; 1987-1989; nam_apap137-5_64 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - YWCA of the USA, 1911-1912; 1918-1919; Undated; nam_apap137-5_65 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Memorabilia, Undated; nam_apap137-6; 7.71 cubic ft.
  This series holds a number of artifacts, banners, handkerchiefs, videotapes, a framed painting, and framed embroidery. Artifacts include pins, posters, ornaments, a gavel, brass plates, and an imprinter with the Albany YWCA seal.
  Arranged by Material.
  - Biblical Quote, Framed Embroidery, 1976; nam_apap137-6_1 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Arab Cookbook in English, Undated; nam_apap137-6_2 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Australian YWCA, Correspondence, 1958; nam_apap137-6_3 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Baghdad YWCA, Correspondence, 1958; nam_apap137-6_4 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Handkerchief, Australian Flowers, ca. 1950s; nam_apap137-6_5 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Handkerchief, Australian Flowers, ca. 1950s; nam_apap137-6_6 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Handkerchief, Australian Koala, ca. 1950s; nam_apap137-6_7 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Handkerchief, Australia Winter Olympics Design, 1956; nam_apap137-6_8 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Handkerchief, New South Wales Design, ca. 1950s; nam_apap137-6_9 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Handkerchief, Nigerian Design, ca. 1950s; nam_apap137-6_10 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Handkerchief, Queensland Design, ca. 1950s; nam_apap137-6_11 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Nigeria YWCA, Correspondence, 1958; nam_apap137-6_12 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - 8mm Tape, unidentified, Undated; nam_apap137-6_13 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - 31st National Convention, Chicago, VHS Tape, 1988; nam_apap137-6_14 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Advertising/Promos, 3/4" Master Tape, 1989; nam_apap137-6_15 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Celebrating 100 Years, VHS Tape, 1988; nam_apap137-6_16 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Public Service Announcements, 3/4" Master Tape, 1988; nam_apap137-6_17 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Public Service Announcements, 3/4" Master Tape, 1989; nam_apap137-6_18 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Public Service Announcements Memo, 1988; nam_apap137-6_19 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Purpose Study, YWCA of the USA, VHS Tape, 1988-1991; nam_apap137-6_20 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Services and Fund Raising Promo, VHS Tape, 1988; nam_apap137-6_21 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Tribute to Women Ceremony, VHS Tape, 1992; nam_apap137-6_22 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Tribute to Women Ceremony, Part 2, VHS Tape, 1992; nam_apap137-6_23 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - YWCA Retirement Fund, VHS Tape, 1989; nam_apap137-6_24 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - YWCA Today, VHS Tape, 1988; nam_apap137-6_25 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Brass Ornaments, Undated; nam_apap137-6_26 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Brass Plaque, 1922; nam_apap137-6_27 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Brass Plaque, 1926; nam_apap137-6_28 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Brass Plaque, Undated; nam_apap137-6_29 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Brass YWCA pins, Undated; nam_apap137-6_30 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Brass YWCA Pins, White and Blue, Undated; nam_apap137-6_31 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - International Women's Day, Patch, Undated; nam_apap137-6_32 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - New York State Council of YWCAs, Gavel, Undated; nam_apap137-6_33 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - "Y-Teen" Stickers, Undated; nam_apap137-6_34 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - YWCA of the USA, Pin, 1993; nam_apap137-6_35 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - YWCA stickers, Undated; nam_apap137-6_36 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Body Conditioning Class, Poster, Undated; nam_apap137-6_37 (Oversized 1, Folder 1)
  - Business Club Dining, Poster, Undated; nam_apap137-6_38 (Oversized 1, Folder 2)
  - Cafeteria, Poster, Undated; nam_apap137-6_39 (Oversized 1, Folder 3)
  - Drawing of YWCA Building, 1989; nam_apap137-6_40 (Oversized 1, Folder 4)
  - Good Fellowship, Poster, Undated; nam_apap137-6_41 (Oversized 1, Folder 5)
  - Group Photo, 1957; nam_apap137-6_42 (Oversized 1, Folder 6)
  - Industrial League, Poster, Undated; nam_apap137-6_43 (Oversized 1, Folder 7)
  - Photograph of Mrs. C. Marshall Munson, 1964; nam_apap137-6_44 (Oversized 1, Folder 8)
  - Purpose Statement, Undated; nam_apap137-6_45 (Oversized 1, Folder 9)
  - Reprint of Lithograph of 1922 YWCA poster, 1983; nam_apap137-6_46 (Oversized 1, Folder 10)
  - "Rooms are Cozy", Poster, Undated; nam_apap137-6_47 (Oversized 1, Folder 11)
  - Sports Skills Class, Poster, Undated; nam_apap137-6_48 (Oversized 1, Folder 12)
  - Thursday Afternoon Club, Poster, Undated; nam_apap137-6_49 (Oversized 1, Folder 13)
  - World Fellowship Committee - poster, Undated; nam_apap137-6_50 (Oversized 1, Folder 14)
  - YWCA "Invest in Her", Poster, Undated; nam_apap137-6_51 (Oversized 1, Folder 15)
  - YWCA Women of the Century Poster, 1985; nam_apap137-6_52 (Oversized 1, Folder 16)
  - Black History Month, Banner, 1991; nam_apap137-6_53 (Oversized 2)
  - Centerport United Methodist Church, Felt Banner, Undated; nam_apap137-6_54 (Oversized 2)
  - Gold Ribbon, Undated; nam_apap137-6_55 (Oversized 2)
  - Maroon, Gold, and Silver Striped Banner, Undated; nam_apap137-6_56 (Oversized 2)
  - World of Difference Banner, Undated; nam_apap137-6_57 (Oversized 2)
  - YWCA of Albany Banner, Undated; nam_apap137-6_58 (Oversized 2)
  - YWCA Sheet, Banner, Undated; nam_apap137-6_59 (Oversized 2)
  - Former YWCA Building, Painting, Undated; nam_apap137-6_60 (Oversized 3)
  - Pueblo YWCA, Poster, ca. 1982; nam_apap137-6_61 (Oversized 3)
  - Tribute to Women, Framed Newspaper, 1994; nam_apap137-6_62 (Oversized 3)
  - Blueprints of Renovation, 1990; nam_apap137-6_63 (Oversized 4)
  - YWCA of the USA, Poster, 1983; nam_apap137-6_64 (Flat-file 1)
  - Our Purpose, Poster, Undated; nam_apap137-6_65 (Flat-file 2)
  - Mrs. Acors Rathbun, Framed Portrait, Undated; nam_apap137-6_66 (Flat-file 3)
  - Seal Imprinter, Undated; nam_apap137-6_67 (Flat-file 3)